cleansheetsallround.co.uk 2014-11-22

# Privacy Statement

**IN RELATION TO CSAR**

This Privacy Policy applies to our website (“the Website”).

By accessing the website, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions whenever you access the website on any device. This Privacy Policy forms part of and is incorporated into our website Terms and Conditions

Any changes to this policy will be posted here. We reserve the right to vary this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall become effective as soon as they are posted. Your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement to all such changes.

We are committed to protecting the personal information you give us and telling you how we use the information we gather about you

**WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU**

We want to offer you a service which you want to use. We may use information about you to help us customise the website, to remember you and to improve its usefulness to you. We may use this information to notify you about changes to the website or products, services or promotions of ours and others (with your consent) that we think you might find of interest. It can also help us to choose articles and services we think will interest you.

Information about you helps us sell space to advertisers of products and services relevant to you so that we can continue to fund the website through advertising and you can continue to use the website for free.

We may send you administrative and promotional emails relating to the website and updates about the website.

We may personalise your visits to the website and develop the design and style of the website to improve the services provided to you.

We may need to contact you to about a comment you have submitted or material you have posted on the website or in order to verify your identity form time to time.

In addition to the services we provide on this website we may want to offer you goods and services provided by us and others (with your consent) which are of interest to you.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**

We may collect information from you when you fill in an online registration form for any of the services available on our website, (eg competitions). We may also collect information you give us over the telephone or in written or other communications. The type of information we will collect includes, for example, your name, mailing address, email address, telephone numbers and gender.

We collect information about your use of the website and services it offers through “cookies”. For more information on “cookies” please see our Cookie Policy which forms part of this Privacy Policy.

In addition to personal information, we may also collect information about you automatically when you visit the website by using cookies (small text files) trends which we may make use of ourselves, or pass to our associated companies or to unconnected parties and our advertising partner may also use cookies to serve advertisements that it believes are most likely to be of use or interest to you. For more information about cookies, including how to turn this feature off, please visit our Cookie Policy

**HOW WE ENSURE PRIVACY IS MAINTAINED**

We endeavour to ensure that your data is stored securely and to prevent unauthorised access. We have security measures in place to protect your information which we monitor regularly. Unfortunately, despite our measures, because of the nature of the internet, we cannot guarantee that your information will remain at all times 100% secure. The continuing efforts of hackers to defeat even the newest of security systems means that we can never make this promise.

Please be aware that if you disclose information on chat areas, your profile page, comment areas, forums or other public services it may be possible for other people to use this information. We are not responsible for the disclosure of any information you post in this way.

We comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 and all other legislation which governs the maintenance of privacy in your information.

The website provides a number of links to websites not operated by us or by companies associated with us. We take no responsibility for the use of any information about you which is collected as a result of your use of these websites and this privacy policy does not extend to any website operated by anybody other than us.

**DISCLOSING YOUR INFORMATION AND YOUR CONSENT**

We will not make use of your personal information for direct marketing activities, or supply this information to third parties for their direct marketing activities without your consent. By direct marketing activities, we mean the communication directly to particular individuals (by e-mail, post or telephone) of any advertising or marketing material.

If having given your consent you subsequently decide you no longer wish to receive direct marketing or information from us or our associated companies or third parties or no longer want us to pass your information to third parties, please notify us at the following email address: admin@cleansheetsallround.co.uk.

We may disclose details about use of the website to other businesses e.g. to demonstrate patterns of use to advertisers and other business partners. The information we pass on will not include any personal information by which you may be identified.

We compile anonymous records of user trends which we may make use of ourselves, or pass to our associated companies.

We will comply with any court order requesting or requiring the disclosure of the identity or location of or any other information in relation to anyone who has accessed the website and we may also disclose such information where we are advised by our lawyers that a court order would be granted requiring us to disclose it, even if no legal proceedings have been commenced in relation to the same.

We endeavour to prevent unauthorised disclosures of your personal information by other people, but we are not responsible for any unauthorised disclosures or other breaches of security or for the actions of others if the information was passed to them with your authority or with the authority of anybody other than us or our associated companies.

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.
